| | Created By | |
Panos Tzimas - Art, Lead Design, Original Concept
&&
Sebastian Nigro - Programming, Co-Design


| | Special Thanks | |

Our awesome beta testers who helped us sort through many
bugs and improve the gameplay.

-Beta Testers-
Callan Hughes a.k.a (Gardraphius) <-- This guy is #1 in my heart and really helped shape the game
Plaxus
Seph
9ine
Seb

| | ( ◞･౪･) Special, SPECIAL Thanks ( ◞･౪･) | |

-Sebastian Nigro-
Thank you Adonis Williams for the awesome character descriptions and moral support.
I'd like to especially thank all of my friends and family for providing me with
positive support and feedback along the way.
A very VERY special thanks to Jesselle De Jesus for being such an amazing person
throughout all of this and encouraging me through this entire project's development.

-Panos Tzimas-
First and foremost I want to thank my family for supporting me all this time from the
very early days of metalhead tycoon back in 2013 through the development of rock god tycoon.
Thank you Nick Grey for collaborating with us and helping us out with the music side 
of the game. Of course none of this music related things would have happened without
the help of Chris Avgerinos so a I owe a big thank you to you too.